{
    "id": "a0225f6feb434ccc812253468534ce5d",
    "title": "Grammar exercise: about, of, on and off",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "6959cae410714014810bbb321a1d934e",
            "title": "About, Off, On And Of",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Did you hear …………….. the explosion at the mall?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "about",
                        "of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "That song reminds me …………………. my childhood.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "off",
                        "of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She complained ………………….. his rude behavior.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "about",
                        "off",
                        "over"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "They took him to hospital when he complained …………………. chest pain and uneasiness.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "of",
                        "on",
                        "over"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He warned me ……………….. dire consequences.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "off",
                        "of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Have you heard …………………. him?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did you think ………………… his latest film?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "of",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We haven’t decided but we are thinking ……………….. moving to a bigger home.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "about",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wouldn’t dream …………………. doing something like that.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "about",
                        "of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I had never thought ………………… it before.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}